Thank you.
In connection with our representatives, I'd like to introduce you to our representative, Chief Executive, Alessandro Ruggio.
Welcome again to the Natatorium at the Nanjing Olympic Sports Centre.
Our first medals in the diving are ready to be handed out here as the women prepare to compete in the final of the 10 metre platform competition.
Well, the preliminary round at 10 meters was certainly interesting.
Word may quickly have spread around Nanjing, but the local girl looks set for a display you do not want to miss.
Wu Shengping looks superb, but diving puts the competitors into the harshest of spotlights.
Disaster literally one slip away.
Wu's rivals will know they simply have to concentrate on their own game, but let's hope that this medal that's on offer here
will be decided by outstanding performances and not on mistakes very encouraging crowd has made their way into the natatorium here
Excellent facility, part of the big complex here at the Olympic Sports Centre.
Already staged six very entertaining days of swimming competition and now the attention turns to five days in all on the diving boards on the platform and springboard.
China, of course, the world superpower in diving.
Certainly they can claim a historic background as well, going right back a thousand years.
Some of the earliest diving they reckon came from performers who used to launch themselves into the water from a swing and then perform their manoeuvres.
Fast forward a thousand years and they are absolutely dominant.
Well a reminder of the format here for the final of the women's 10 meter platform.
They had a busy eight rounds of diving in the preliminary competition.
The first four rounds involved dives with a limit on the total degree of difficulty and those earlier marks are carried forward into this final.
Now they have four more dives with no restrictions to decide who gets up on that podium at the far end of the pool.
China of course overwhelmingly the dominant country in world diving especially on their own patch 2008 Beijing Olympic Games seven out of eight gold medals 2011 in Shanghai at the World Championships ten out of ten gold medals This is the dive order for this final
Eleven competitors, four rounds remember.
And Wu Shengping, the local heroine here from Nanjing, will dive last.
Lo Zhai Yi of Malaysia, also very impressive this morning.
Unusual this in junior competition compared to the seniors that the marks are carried forward.
Did make this morning's competition that bit more competitive rather than just deciding on the dive order here for these competitors.
They'd have a long wait if they traveled with the rest of their teams here because we've had a week of competition and finally they get a chance to get into the pool.
They will have been relieved this morning to get a feel for this superb facility.
Maybe time to check up on a few wishes.
All the best.
We'll see one or two of them putting on their iPods, or similar, to listen to the music, go into their own zone.
This will be short and sharp though.
Four rounds, remember.
Eleven competitors.
The action will keep on going.
and they will be very pleased to finally get this final underway.
Katyalina Vitsna from Belarus will get us underway in the two and a half somersault pint, 2.8 the tariff.
There is quite a variety in the difficulty of the dives for some of these young divers who are at different stages of their careers.
Here we go in the first diving final here at Nanjing 2014.
The 16-year-old from Minsk took her time in her dives in the preliminary competition.
One or two rushed there rather, she was quite composed.
Just a little bit of over rotation there as she went into the water.
tight, piked position and just started to go wrong towards the end there.
Want to put those brakes on for that core strength comes into play.
Three fives, 42 points.
A modest start there.
Salah Carolina Pérez Beltran from Colombia.
Back to two and a half somersault, half twist.
That is 2.6.
Recap on the scoring here as the crowd responding well to that dive there from the Colombian girl.
Seven judges, top two, bottom two marks are discounted.
The middle three then are multiplied by the degree of difficulty or the tariff to give you a points score.
It's a tidy enough execution there.
55-90 for the Colombian.
Remember these marks are added on to the totals of the first four rounds this morning.
Young Molly Carlson from Canada.
Not 16 till next month, but the youngest diver here at the Games.
forward three and a half somersault well she got the spin speed she might have been looking for but the downside of that was stopping it looking to get through those rotations as soon as possible to leave the room to open out into the perfect entry position you can see the legs coming over there and slapping onto the water
And 43.20, not the return she was looking for.
From Egypt, Mahahuda.
Forward three and a half, somersault tucked.
It's her opening dive in this final.
She had quite an encouraging preliminary competition.
Remember, there are no indoor diving pools in Egypt, which really handicaps her training opportunities, especially during the winter.
So this environment is very much a new experience for her.
Again that over rotation of entry just leaving a bad impression there with the judges and she gets three sixes 48 60 It's not all down to the entry, but that is the last thing the judges see and it can really influence Gratia laden Mahoney is from the United States She is from Newton, Massachusetts
There's two and a half somersault tucked.
That's quite an encouraging opening dive from her.
Again, the divers are finding it tough as the swirling to just hold that entry position nice and clean all the way through the water.
But in general, she's made a decent job of that with 63 points.
Ingrid de Oliveira from Brazil.
she won bronze at the qualifying event in Guadalajara back in March quite showing her best in the preliminary competition now she's got a back two and a half sun assault won the half twist that's worth 3.2
through that twist early on needing to get into the pike position a little bit hurried through that and again the entry not really held as vertically as she would have hoped so she's down in the 6.5s and scores 62.40
She looks very nice this morning.
Had one lapse but looks stylish and very elegant.
I'm getting good applause from the crowd but again the entry was the weakest part.
The judges will be looking for all the stages of the dive.
The lift off the platform, the pike position and then finally the entry.
Well, she's made a decent job of that.
She could be in there competing for a medal if she hits her best.
Gonna prize Noshnik from Ukraine, 18 year old from Kiev.
Most of these girls also competing at three meters here with an inward two and a half somersault piked.
It brings quite a bit of experience into this competition, having competed at World Championship level.
Not being rushed.
To find that trigger.
This is a long hold.
Time to go.
Was it worth the wait?
10 out of 10 for Composure.
She was unlucky in Barcelona in the World Championships.
She was 13th in the semi-final, missed out on a place in the final by just one place.
and seven and a half so they need to bring in 64 40 so that long way to the top was pretty well worth it
Alejandro Orozco Loffa the Olympic silver medalist at 10 meters the youngest Olympic medalist in Mexican history at London 2012 when she was just 15 years of age she has got real pedigree and I don't think we completely saw that this morning.
Inward three and a half somersault tucked
But this time in the final, it's all for real.
3.2.
I think that was a bit more the sort of show we were looking for in the preliminary.
Although the first four rounds did count, then the drivers could afford to keep a little bit in the tank.
Good entry position, pulling it right the way through the water.
Just a bit heavy, maybe.
Three sevens, steady opening, not a dazzling one, but the high tariff will give her 67.20.
Lo Jai from Malaysia.
Four years ago in Singapore, Panda Leila.
from malaysia made her mark here with two silvers they went on to become an olympic medalist and be a real superstar in malaysia their diving is on a big up for the three and a half somersault there
Very stylish competitor.
She looked in the preliminaries, quite a way back from the edge of the platform.
Really good, tight pike position.
Reaching out for the water, holding it all the way through.
That was nice.
Quick spin speed.
No wonder she's smiling with 73.50 there.
The judges were edging towards generous.
Let's see how they react.
Cue the applause for Wu Shengping, the local girl from Nanjing who was superb this morning.
Don't play poker against her, she doesn't give much away.
Forward three and a half somersault.
Two things to listen for there, just how quiet the entry was and how quick the applause responded.
Plenty of height there, quickly through the rotations.
Really tight in that pike position, holds her form all the way through into the water.
Three nines, slams down her opening score, 81 points.
Her four dives in the preliminary in this section were all 80 plus and she's at it again.
She is going to take some catching.
Remember those marks are high because they had the first four rounds this morning added on but Wu Shengping is often storming.
Ladies and gentlemen, please remain quiet and continue to walk.
Thank you for your hard work.
The announcer there just asking for quiet when the divers come to the board, curb their natural enthusiasm.
Crowds at these games have been enthusiastic, but even in China they don't get the chance to enjoy this standard of competition that often.
Anxious coaches.
Round two of four.
Katsyarina Pitsna of Belarus.
With a forward three and a half somersault tucked.
2.7.
She didn't really get through the full movements before she hit the water.
Just coming up rather short.
And a fairly untidy entry unfortunately for her.
A lot of water, big splash.
Down in the fives, 40.5.
Sarah Carolina Perez Beltran from Colombia.
She didn't compete at the qualifying event in Guadalajara in Mexico, when divers could grab the place either for themselves or their country.
Forward three and a half somersault.
Again, not really able to hit the anchors.
It's that core strength which in these younger divers is not fully developed yet.
That's what they need to just hold that position after the speed of the summer salting.
And you can see the rotations carrying on there, hence the messy entry there, and he's down in the 4.5s.
A word from the coach just explaining what needs to be done.
big day for these divers.
Molly Carlson not on a limb in Canadian diving being from Thunder Bay in Ontario the divers very much concentrated in Quebec and in Montreal so she has to work somewhat remotely
This, I think, was a new dive for her.
Another unusual technique of getting into this armstand position.
Got to show the judges she's in full control.
Try and get spring off the arms and through the legs.
Well, it's a 3.3 tariff dive, so plenty of ambition from the 15-year-old.
but the entry was um tidy not yet behaving with the body strength to get as much lift off the platform as she really needs good to see her coming up smiling and enjoying it three fours though that's not quite so good with her coach explaining maharudha 16 year old
was only able to compete in mexico for the qualifier because she got her exams out the way coach she has where there is an interesting chap professorship in microbiology arm stand forward double somersault here show the control first that's a good starting position
Well, not a lot of snap out of the arm stand but she controlled it well and got herself into a good position for the entry.
She's made a fairly tidy job of that.
The dive can be broken down into stages so they can work on it all the way through and that is a nice entry position.
And the judges think so as well, which is even more important.
She got some eight fives, three eights to count.
Well done.
Gracia Layden Mahoney.
Got the bronze at three meters in the qualifier.
This world junior champion on the springboard in 2012.
competing at both heights.
Inward three and a half somersault 3.2.
It started well but didn't finish in quite the same way.
good position there through the somersaults but never got into the right shape to make a clean entry.
Just lost it there and couldn't get those legs in a good vertical position.
And three 4.5s for a modest 43.20.
Put it behind you, move on, that's the message.
Ingrid de Oliveira She has a FINA ranking among the seniors 30th at 10 meters 18 years of age again with that unusual side starting position to get into the arm stand for the back double somersault one-and-a-half twist extra support on those wrists nice position long hold
And again, it's just a slightly untidy finish to the dive.
Just coming up short, running out of height a bit.
But...
I know it's a disaster.
Two sevens and a six five for 65-60 from a 3.2 degree of difficulty.
L.A. Jaloni from Rennes in France showed in the preliminary that she can produce a very stylish dive.
She's got an inward two and a half somersault which is down at 2.8 degree of difficulty.
Now she could be pushing for a medal if she can just reproduce some of the form from the preliminary.
nice clean sound on the entry she doesn't uh doesn't hang around when she gets into her position and did seem to rush a couple of her dives in the preliminary but she is a very attractive figure through the water and she's made a good job of that the judge is giving three eights there there were there was one eight point five as well
And that's done her no harm.
Some of the divers liking to put a towel on the end of the platform there to give them just a bit more confidence for the grip before this forward three and a half somersault.
They also like to towel themselves down and get dry, often to give themselves a bit more grip when they get into a piked position, really get a good hold on the thighs and keep the position really tight.
Full concentration here.
She seems to get a good bit of extra height off the platform.
again can compete right across the the range from one meter just that entry became a little untidy that links could have been a bit tighter together and would have been a bit cleaner but it's 5850 from three six point fives for the Ukrainian
Alejandro Arasco Lofa from Mexico, the Olympic silver medalist in the synchro event at this height with Paola Espinosa.
On stand back double somersault, one and a half twist, 3.2 the degree of difficulty.
with control into the gymnastic position.
She's ranked 14 in the world, so would have come here with real expectation of being up on that podium.
Just feels she's not hit her very best so far.
And those marks confirm it.
68.80.
She's still going to be up there competing.
Hello, Zhai Yi from Malaysia.
Competed at the recent Commonwealth Games.
She was in the 10-metre platform where she finished 8th and also synchronised 3-metre event where she finished 5th.
So great experience for her only a few weeks ago.
Back to a half somersault, half a twist.
Good pike position.
Not a bad entry either.
Very nice position there.
Not quite pulling the dive all the way through the water.
The divers can do a lot of work once they hit the water to complete the dive, but that's still 59.80.
A decent return from a 2.6 tariff dive.
Now the buzz goes around this arena.
Wu Shengping in with three and a half somersault tucked.
3.2 the degree of difficulty.
Well she was always going to get a great response from the crowd but such is the depth.
Chinese diving that Huang Xiaowei won the qualifying competition at 10 meters won the recent World Cup which is the biggest event of the year and this is another diver who seems to be able to churn out the big scores one after the other so consistent so far look at that three nines again 86 40 top quality top consistency
Wu Shengping really is in a class of her own.
She's already got 61 points plus as a lead, but Lo and Orofko Lofa putting themselves in the medal positions after two of four rounds.
No hold up in the tempo of the competition.
Diving events with the charge of Fina.
The world governing body are very, very tightly run.
The girls positioned on different steps of the 10 meter platform to be ready to step up there and compete as soon as possible.
There's no drop in the pace.
Katja Rina-Fitzner of Belarus.
arm stand back double somersault half a twist 2.7 again as she looks to get the control in that position good hold any extra height you can get with the push-off will really
give them more chance of getting through the rotations and getting into the right entry position.
You can just see from that frontal angle she was falling away rather at right angles there.
And 3.55s, 44.55.
This is proving an experience for the young diver, but we're not really up there competing for the medals.
Perez Beltran from Colombia who also have a tradition of producing strong teams for big international competitions.
17 year old has a back two and a half somersault, piked 2.9.
And a very positive start to that dive.
You can really see her tense and throw herself into her somersaults.
But you've got a bit untidy again towards the entry point, just as she unwinds.
And you can just see again, doesn't really hold the entry position.
Three sixes, 52.20.
Good to see her enjoying the whole experience.
so important these young divers like Molly Castle at 15 to absorb everything from the competitive experience.
The coaches I've spoken to have been so impressed with the facilities here in Nanjing and the way they've been received as well.
Back two and a half sun assault piked 2.9
well the crowd reaction said everything about that execution you can feel the crowd willing every diver to really try and reflect what they're capable of but young molly not quite managing that into the piked position just to get the forward just a bit more tucked in there and never really getting out into correct entry position
two, three and a halfs and a four to count 31.90.
Take the experience out of it.
Maha Buddha was down in seventh place after her first two dives.
And he manages to train once or maybe twice a week.
hoping that Egyptian diving can start to push on and that the more they take part in these sort of competitions, the more they'll be able to push four facilities.
Well, Maha has shown in some of her dives she's got real potential.
2.8 the DD there very nice pikes position for it there right onto her legs and she's made a pretty tidy job of that the two sevens and a seven and a half good to see if she can get consistency right across her program
Gracia Layden Mahoney.
She's been competing in the World Series and at Grand Prix events this year on the FINA calendar.
Usually in the synchronized events.
These individual competitions put so much more pressure on the divers.
Armstand back double somersault, one and a half twists.
3.2.
Up a lonely higher degree of difficulty dives.
He's been world junior champion at three meters.
Springboard is her stronger discipline.
Decent enough effort there from the American though.
Two sevens and a six five.
Tracy Bird is the coach there having a word with her.
Ingrid de Oliveira.
I think she qualified for this competition she said it was the beginning of a great dream for her for a forward three and a half somersault pike tier 3.0
Good spin speed there in her rotations.
Committed totally to the dive.
Just not quite able again to get into that entry position.
Let's see what the judges think.
They're pretty unanimous.
Three 6.5s, 58.50.
Now, can L.A. Kehlanyi produce something impressive and get herself in medal contention?
Arm stand, back double somersault, half a twist.
Tariff is down at 2.7, so she really needs to make a clean job of this one.
Now there's no rush.
She did hurry things in the preliminary.
All the way back from the edge of that platform.
Just feels she could have done with a little bit of extra height off the platform, but very hard for these girls to really get the push out of the arms that just might make a bit of a difference.
But it was a nice entry.
2.7.5 and a 7.59.40.
Just outside the medal positions, I fear.
Kajaloslik.
The first two and a half somersault here.
Very good European Junior Championships.
fourth at one meter just missed out on a bronze got silver at 10 meters so her confidence should be decent she's in fourth place just trying to get onto that podium she does take a long time
Increasing attention here.
This is a long long wait.
It might just be her personal style.
she does go she makes a very positive movement at the top of her dive trying to get extra height it's quite a lot of her to get into a tight tucked position but again you can see the entry there was at quite an angle and there was a big splash and a low return on the scoreboard with three falls
Roscoe Lofa, can she improve on her bronze position going into this third of four dives?
That might have been just a bit more like it.
First part of the dive, decent enough.
Good quick rotations.
It was just a bit heavy, the backs of her leg and the entry there.
Just could have got a little bit tighter maybe, no she does tighten up.
But again it was just an untidy entry with the ankles there, the heels slapping the water.
Two six and a halfs and a seven.
Just feel this water come from her.
Loh Chye from Malaysia.
Two silvers for Malaysia four years ago from Panda Leila, who she admits is her big hero.
Malaysia had a very good Commonwealth Games.
The men's team were starting to get up to the same standards that the women have set.
Arm stand back, double somersault, one and a half twist.
Well there's an instinctive neatness to her diving.
She's very slight.
103 pounds, 47 kilos, she weighs just five foot three.
and she always seems to slice her way into the water.
Steady two sevens and a seven point five sixty eight eighty.
Now the standard setter here Wu Shengping
Can she maintain the sky-high standards she's been setting since competition opened here?
Arm stand back double somersault, one and a half twist, 3.2 the tariff for the local star.
Very quickly and confidently into that arm stand position.
Well no wonder she's confident you'd be as well if you could produce consistent diving of the standard we've seen from her so far, the 17 year old.
Not the best entry that we've seen from Wu so far but
It's going to be well enough to keep her at the top of the pack.
Two eights and a 7.5, 75-20.
She has dipped below 80 points for the first time.
She's not too harsh on herself.
China, Malaysia, Mexico in the medal positions there.
Could be tight for the silver, but it looks all over at the top of the pack.
Carlsson the back marker at the moment the youngest diver.
Very good crowd indeed in here for this first of five finals in the diving pool.
That surprised the Chinese supporters turn out with the standard they can expect from their own competitors.
The final round of four then here in this final of the women's 10 meter platform competition.
Katja Fittsner from Belarus.
10th out of 11 after three rounds.
She's only competing on the platform so she'll want to sign off here with a nice clean back two and a half somersault with half twist.
Unfortunately she couldn't do that.
Competing since she was nine years of age.
We always want them to finish off on a high note and come away with a feeling of satisfaction for their day's work.
Link's just a bit bent on that pike position.
She knows she can do better than that.
Three, four, fives, just 35 points to end.
Perez Beltran of Colombia.
Big hero is Orlando Duque, who is a famous high diver, as in 27 meters.
Leave you to think about that height.
The young 17 year old though has enough to deal with on that 10 meter platform.
In with three and a half somersault, 3.2.
Up among the high tariff dives.
Looking for a nice tidy finish to her program.
You can't help but just flinch when you know it doesn't work out for the divers.
Everybody wants to see a really good standard of performance.
If they can, rather than mistakes, they're going to affect the standings.
But this is very much a learning experience.
Diving is a tough sport.
You have to produce on the day and they have to learn that.
No hiding place, 48 points.
She's back to the three metre event as well.
Molly Carlson got the place that had not been won in the qualifying competition because Canadian female diving in particular is extremely strong.
This will have been a big experience for her.
She's back at three meters.
Reverse two and a half somersault to complete her four dive program.
It was a little bit better.
Again, it was the entry position that gave her problems.
She has ambition out of the pool as well, wants to go on and get a business degree.
Down in the five fives and the five for 44-84 Molly.
We'll see her again later in the games.
Mahat Budha is also competing at both heights.
best junior diver in Egypt forward two and a half somersault one twist in sixth place which would be an encouraging performance you can just see the competition through she has been pretty consistent which is always encouraging you can just roll out the big mistake dives then you're always going to give yourself a chance of
just reflecting your own particular skill set.
One of the taller divers here, which will mean that when she gets it right she will cut an impressive figure.
Seven and two six point fives.
Not a bad effort.
Gratia Leydon Mahoney for her fourth dive for the 18-year-old.
Q2 at 5.7 is one of the taller divers.
There's too many divers.
Started in gymnastics, so played a bit of ice hockey.
Not many divers do that.
Back one half, some assault, three and a half twists.
Three point three, big twister.
She said herself quite a lot to get through before she hit the water.
Ending up just trying to hurry herself through it, having to change position for the arms to punch a hole for the rest of her to follow.
Just coming up a little bit short there.
Five and two, five and a half there.
Again she's competing on the springboard.
Ingrid de Oliveira from Brazil.
Fifth.
Fairway back from a podium position.
But, who knows?
18 years of age.
From Brom's qualifying event.
Not quite reproduced that threat here when it's really mattered.
In with three and a half somersault.
Nice sounding entry there.
Tight tucked position.
Just couldn't hold the entry all the way through.
There's a lot of work they can do under the water, pulling the legs through, making sure they complete the dive as impressively as possible.
Two 5.5s and a 6 there, 54.40 for Ingrid.
Just out of the medal positions.
2.8 is the tariff here for the young French girl.
Back one and a half, two and a half twist.
2.8.
She needs to execute this one as well as she can and just see what happens again very quickly into her dive.
It might just be her personal style, but you fear that she might just rush it a little bit up there.
The coach said top six would be a very good return for her efforts.
Jenny made her international debut at full level this year, so this is all priceless experience.
Two sevens and a six point five.
probably not quite enough to get into the medal stakes but progress 18 years of age from Kiev at the National University of Physical Training and Education forward two and a half somersault one twist piked
Well, Ukrainian diving is definitely progressing, often competing for the medals at highest level.
Even so, she says that her big heroes are Wu Min-Shar and Chen Rao-Lin, the two outstanding Chinese divers.
So she believes in setting her sights high.
Three sixes there, 52.24 gana.
Three to go, and we're really now down among the medal contenders.
What color will they be diving for?
The Olympic Synchro Silver Medalist from London 2012, Alejandra Orozco Loffa from Mexico.
Back two and a half sun salt, one and a half twists, piked.
3.2 is a high DD.
Well has she saved her best points return till last.
Won't she get in there and improve on her third position going into this final round.
Don't think that the entry was quite as impressive.
Though you can see from that angle a much bigger splash.
Down in the six fives.
62.
That will still get her a medal.
Loh Zhaoyi, the 16 year old from Malaysia, just 5 foot 3.
This is to confirm a silver medal for Malaysia, even with three and a half somersault then 3.2.
Very nice entry, really clean sounding dive.
don't think there's quite enough of her to make what you might call a rip.
But she slides into the water, a very elegant figure, just a little bit angled across there when we looked at it from that replay.
The judges don't see those replays, remember, but there is a very nice impression overall about her diving, and she's got two seven and a halves and an eight, and she's got a very big smile, and she has got herself a silver medal.
It has been a one-woman show, and here she is.
Wu Shengping has been supreme.
This is one to enjoy.
Can she really nail it at the final dive of the competition?
Back two and a half somersault, one and a half twist, 3.2.
Well, the gold medalist from start to finish.
The local girl comes good big style.
Just a little bit heavier on the entry, but you've really got to look for the faults.
Opening out and pulling the dive all the way through.
No wonder she smiles.
8.5s, 81.60, a big hug and she has kept up those sky-high Chinese standards.
China are often running with the gold for Wu Shengping.
Malaysia get an impressive silver through Lo and Orozco Lothar gets the bronze, the Olympic silver medalist.
Well, who is going to stop these Chinese divers sweeping the board as they did in Singapore?
A double-double for them.
Wu Shengping will be back at three meters.
And how do you stop such an irresistible force?
Well, the diving competition is up and running.
And if you're not familiar with the Chinese national anthem, you may well be over the next few days.
Ladies and gentlemen, ladies and gentlemen, ladies and gentlemen, ladies and gentlemen, ladies and gentlemen,
Yeah.
Thank you.
I think I found a little bit of a mark.
Yeah.
Thank you.
you you
Thank you for watching the show.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Well, we've had our first taste of a diving final here at the Natatorium.
And certainly the former World Junior Champion has put on a great show.
It is an endless production line of outstanding competitors.
And this crowd is really looking forward now to this victory ceremony for the Women's 10m platform event.
Oh.
Hurry up and use the double pass, huh huh huh hey Hurry up and use the double pass, huh huh huh hey Who doesn't know the world?
Who doesn't know the world?
Hurry up and use the double pass, huh Hurry up and use the double pass, huh Hurry up and use the double pass, huh Hurry up and use the double pass, huh Hurry up and use the double pass, huh
What's your name
Ladies and gentlemen, the victory ceremony for the women's tennis platform.
Ladies and gentlemen, the second season of the Summer Youth Olympic Games is about to begin.
Please welcome the medalists.
The first victory ceremony in the diving competition at Nanjing 2014.
And the locals have got exactly what they wanted.
A local victory.
The 17-year-old from Nanjing, absolutely dominant in her own backyard.
She moved this pool pretty well.
But you've got a feeling that wasn't the big difference.
The medals will be presented by Mr. Bernard Rassmann, Brazil, member of the International Olympic Committee, Olympia World Supermedals, accompanied by Ms. Jesus Manna, representing the Federation International Denatation.
The medalist is a member of the International Olympic Committee.
He is a former Olympic athlete who has broken through the European and US Olympics.
He is a member of the national team from Brazil, Mr. Daniel Zeman.
Together with him, the medalist is a member of the international swimming team, Mr. Jesus Reina.
Future looking promising for Mexico with a bronze individual medal to add to her Olympic silver Synchro medal for Alejandra Orozco
17 years of age.
Mexican diving continues to be strong.
Malaysian diving continues to go from strength to strength.
Loh Jai following in the pioneering footsteps of Panda Leila Rinong who won two silvers in Singapore four years ago and now this 16 year old has another silver for the Malaysian collection after a very
impressive display world junior champion Chinese national champion now the youth olympic champion never in doubt
From the first time she stepped up onto that platform.
An outstanding performance from an outstanding prospect.
More than 75 points the winning margin.
And at last she allows herself a big smile.
Ladies and gentlemen, please stand for the anthem of People's Republic of China.
Ladies and gentlemen, please stand
Well, if you're lucky enough to go to major international diving competitions, that is the anthem you hear time after time after time.
What a big crowd has come out to support the local girl.
And she rewarded them all the way with an outstanding performance.
Wu Shengping wins the gold medal by a street.
Plenty of encouragement though from the silver and bronze medalists.
We'll be seeing more of them as well.
Four years ago it was Liu Xiao who got double gold in the women's competition.
The great Choo Bo dominated before the men in Singapore.
Are we going to get another double-double here in Nanjing?
One down, four to go for China if they're going to sweep the board here.
These supporters have really enjoyed.